{
  "results": [
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "C Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "C#/D Flat Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "D Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "D#/E Flat Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "E Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "F Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "F#/G Flat Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "G Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "G#/A Flat Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "A Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "A#/B Flat Major"
  },
  {
    "category": "scale",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What key is this scale in?",
    "correct_answer": "B/C Flat Major"
  }
  ]
}
